Orange: you know pump the brakes here
Orange: what are we talking about
Orange: oh people thought the box is my crush no
Orange: no no no no vox is not my crush box is a
Orange: very good friend nothing more nothing
Orange: less he is very important to me as a
Orange: friend he is not a crush
and it was a super chat that said the
box was a crush i don't blame people for
crashing on box he's a very very
charming man but
me and vox we are just friends
[Music]
i love everybody of me to send to ian
very platonically everybody is amazing
in their own way
vox is lovely
but sometimes
he needs to be put in his place
but i have gotten used to it sometimes
i'm just gonna be like
i have my dude
you gotta pop the brakes
gotta chill out there for a second
he knows it and i know it
everybody knows it
[Music]
exactly he needs to be hit with a bunk
he's a beat with a bunk
my drink is a little bit room
temperature right now i'm not very fond
of that i'll be right back i need to get
another ice let me put that down there
i'll be right back
[Music]
my baits
stop saving for the chair
oh
hello
i'm back
[Music]
oh yeah
bro wedding girl wedding completely
platonic wedding
does that ever happened
just two like like two best friends just
getting married for the of it i
mean vegas is a thing